[{"answer": "Well, they were saying stuff like, \"Go kill yourself.", "docId": "131018pmt", "aSentId": 41, "question": "Where does it move from that to the severity of what has happened here, in other words where there's a genuine risk that somebody may take their life?", "qSentId": 40}, {"answer": "Unfortunately, there's not a lot of responsibility put on parent's shoulders to the way their kids act online.", "docId": "131018pmt", "aSentId": 60, "question": "Where does it lie at the moment and where do you think it should be?", "qSentId": 59}, {"answer": "Well, Piers, you can get access to it.", "docId": "131018pmt", "aSentId": 87, "question": "How do you regulate what you can't get access to?", "qSentId": 86}, {"answer": "I don't think they can be for every word.", "docId": "131018pmt", "aSentId": 111, "question": "At the same time, having had, you know, three teenage kids, how far can you really say parents have to be legally responsible to every word they may post on social media?", "qSentId": 110}, {"answer": "Piers, I absolutely do.", "docId": "131018pmt", "aSentId": 128, "question": "How far do you take it?", "qSentId": 127}, {"answer": "Well, Piers, there's one thing that's very much missing from this conversation and that is a whole lot more support for the victim of the bullying or the stalking or both.", "docId": "131018pmt", "aSentId": 171, "question": "What should the law do about it?", "qSentId": 170}, {"answer": "Well, it's very hard because you have to balance on the one hand freedom of speech and freedom of expression against the very understandable needs of the victim.", "docId": "131018pmt", "aSentId": 176, "question": "What is the best sensible way to frame a law that can deal with it?", "qSentId": 175}, {"answer": "Well, first of all I have a 15 year old and an eight year old.", "docId": "131018pmt", "aSentId": 196, "question": "What is your thinking on all this from your crisis point of view?", "qSentId": 195}, {"answer": "Yes, and that's exactly what I said on your show the other night.", "docId": "131018pmt", "aSentId": 216, "question": "Is that your man from Harvard?", "qSentId": 215}, {"answer": "I'm going to make that happen if it kills me.", "docId": "131018pmt", "aSentId": 230, "question": "Can I pay (ph) for that?", "qSentId": 229}, {"answer": "First of all, beware of people who are dismissing him and beware of people who impugn his motives and I grant him sincerity and I'm a great believer in assuming somebody is sincere and just sincerely disagreeing with his views.", "docId": "131018pmt", "aSentId": 250, "question": "What do you make of him?", "qSentId": 249}, {"answer": "Well, I think he's very bright but unless the GOP is on some kind of suicide mission where they would like to just go off in flames in the next election, I would say that they're not going to nominate him for president that he does obviously represent a lot of people in the Tea Party and some people in Texas who are also very conservative.", "docId": "131018pmt", "aSentId": 256, "question": "Are you impressed by what you see in here just in terms of the way he conducts (ph) himself?", "qSentId": 255}, {"answer": "I think we need to correct the system and make it easier for people to have access, but no.", "docId": "131018pmt", "aSentId": 295, "question": "Should she still be in her job given the pretty upholding breakdown of the ObamaCare system, if she's on her watch?", "qSentId": 294}, {"answer": "Only people fainting at her and her rallies are going to be chubby gals from now.", "docId": "131018pmt", "aSentId": 336, "question": "Even Hillary Clinton?", "qSentId": 335}, {"answer": "I kind of hope so.", "docId": "131018pmt", "aSentId": 338, "question": "Do you think she will be the democrat nominee?", "qSentId": 337}, {"answer": "Obama.", "docId": "131018pmt", "aSentId": 345, "question": "Who do you most fear on the Democrats side?", "qSentId": 344}, {"answer": "Well, that remains to be seen.", "docId": "131018pmt", "aSentId": 350, "question": "Who's the most electable right now?", "qSentId": 349}, {"answer": "If he were the republican candidate, OK.", "docId": "131018pmt", "aSentId": 361, "question": "Could he win the election?", "qSentId": 360}, {"answer": "I'm not sure I want to see them in debate.", "docId": "131018pmt", "aSentId": 373, "question": "... who do you think can exercise your desire to have a winner?", "qSentId": 372}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "131018pmt", "aSentId": 389, "question": "Ted Cruz?", "qSentId": 388}, {"answer": "I don't see the analogy but I love them.", "docId": "131018pmt", "aSentId": 392, "question": "Isn't he the new king of the Tea Party where she was once queen?", "qSentId": 391}, {"answer": "Well, see it's very possible.", "docId": "131018pmt", "aSentId": 394, "question": "Yes, but my point is I mean, do you think that he could be more electable to a wider cross section just to win the nomination and mind anything else and republicans?", "qSentId": 393}, {"answer": "No, look at how we've been doing in elections.", "docId": "131018pmt", "aSentId": 398, "question": "And republicans don't to do that?", "qSentId": 397}, {"answer": "I didn't see it.", "docId": "131018pmt", "aSentId": 424, "question": "How did you hear about it?", "qSentId": 423}, {"answer": "I did and I started to cry.", "docId": "131018pmt", "aSentId": 426, "question": "Do you see at home (ph)?", "qSentId": 425}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "131018pmt", "aSentId": 429, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 428}, {"answer": "No, no, I can't.", "docId": "131018pmt", "aSentId": 440, "question": "Do you believe that?", "qSentId": 439}, {"answer": "I'm gay.", "docId": "131018pmt", "aSentId": 450, "question": "What?", "qSentId": 449}, {"answer": "Are you ...", "docId": "131018pmt", "aSentId": 453, "question": "What?", "qSentId": 452}, {"answer": "The time we did that episode we were three seasons in or maybe possible, I think was three.", "docId": "131018pmt", "aSentId": 456, "question": "ORGAN: When you said those words, when you're a straight man, so you're playing a gay character did you have any conception of the enormity of that moment both to the debate we just discussed but also to you and to your career?", "qSentId": 455}, {"answer": "I mean absolutely.", "docId": "131018pmt", "aSentId": 465, "question": "Again, going back to the Biden clip there when you look at Washington and the ridiculous shutdown of the government and squabbling of the debt ceiling, all this stuff we've all have to endure (inaudible) for the last two weeks, do you think that should be some kind of show on television which does for the Washington dysfunction what Will & Grace did for the gay marriage debate and the gay rights debate?", "qSentId": 464}, {"answer": "We've grabbed each other.", "docId": "131018pmt", "aSentId": 493, "question": "A floor and half, it's properly clenched (ph)?", "qSentId": 492}, {"answer": "Nine.", "docId": "131018pmt", "aSentId": 497, "question": "He's nine years old?", "qSentId": 496}, {"answer": "There were nine of us, eight of us something like that.", "docId": "131018pmt", "aSentId": 501, "question": "And how many people are in the elevator?", "qSentId": 500}, {"answer": "It could have.", "docId": "131018pmt", "aSentId": 507, "question": "(Inaudible) limit?", "qSentId": 506}, {"answer": "I'm about to start rehearsal on my first Broadway play.", "docId": "131018pmt", "aSentId": 514, "question": "What you do up to for the moment?", "qSentId": 513}, {"answer": "It does.", "docId": "131018pmt", "aSentId": 518, "question": "But, does it have a name?", "qSentId": 517}, {"answer": "I was starting back on the third season of Perception on TNT.", "docId": "131018pmt", "aSentId": 524, "question": "Eric, what are you up to?", "qSentId": 523}, {"answer": "I totally -- the process was unlike -- the sitcom is unlike anything else.", "docId": "131018pmt", "aSentId": 531, "question": "(Inaudible) with great funness with -- did you miss it?", "qSentId": 530}]